seekyz.com 2006-08-29

# Seekyz.com

Privacy Policy 

Seekyz.com is strongly committed to protecting and ensuring your right to privacy. The following is a disclosure of our privacy policy and explains how Seekyz.com collects, uses, and if necessary, discloses information of Seekyz.com users. It is important that you know and fully understand Seekyz.com's Privacy Policy before using our website. 

Anonymous Information   
In order to improve our services to you and to gain a better understanding of the users of our website, Seekyz.com collects and stores anonymous information such as time of day, browser type, country, search query, and IP address in our server logs whenever you visit Seekyz.com. 

Information Collected by Third Parties   
Throughout our site, an outside ad company displays ads. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our web site, our ad company collects cookies connected with banner ads. We do not have access to this information. 

We make every effort to preserve user privacy, however we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

Links to Other Sites   
Seekyz.com contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Seekyz.com, is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Seekyz.com. 

Cookies   
A �cookie� is a small piece of data stored on the user's computer that identifies you as a unique user. This piece of data contains information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information while using our site. 

Security   
Seekyz.com takes every precaution to protect user information against loss, misuse and alteration. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we pledge to do our utmost to prevent against any such occurrences. 

Notification of Changes   
In the event of a change in our privacy policy, we will post such changes to our privacy policy, homepage, and other places we deem appropriate. Our users are will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection and in our privacy policy, we will notify users via email. 

Contact Information   
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
